wholesaleflowersovernight.com 2013-11-03

# Privacy :: Wholesale Flowers :: Wedding Flowers :: Wholesale Flowers Overnight

_**WFO Privacy Policy**_ We have established this privacy policy so that you can understand how we intend to treat your personal information. We strive to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy.

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit the without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.

We use this information to:

·

Process your order  
·Improve and customize the content and layout of the site and other materials  
·Notify you of updates to the site.  
·Notify you of relevant products and services.  
·Notify you of upcoming events and programs

Under no circumstances will we sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information. We will not rent or sell your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent. We may share such information in any of the following limited circumstances:

•We have your consent.

•We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this privacy policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

•We are required to do so by law

•We have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Wholesale Flowers Overnight Inc. or the public.

While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.

By using this site, you consent to the terms of this privacy policy and our processing of personal information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where we collect personal information on the site. Should the privacy policy change, we will take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on the site for a reasonable period of time.
